healthykitchen101.com 2019-03-30

# Privacy Policy - Healthy Kitchen 101

At **Healthy Kitchen 101** , we recognize the importance of your privacy. Our policy reflects the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit [Healthy Kitchen 101](https://healthykitchen101.com/), and how we safeguard your information.

### **LOG FILES**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files includes your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Google Chrome or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited through our site.

### **COOKIES AND WEB BEACONS**

We never sell your personal information to third parties. However, we use third party advertisements on _Healthy Kitchen 101_ to support our site. Some of these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which allows them access to information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes or showing certain ads based on your interests.

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in your browser. However, this can affect your ability to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include difficulty logging in to services or programs, such as forums or accounts.

## **ADVERTISING PRIVACY STATEMENT**

This site is affiliated with AdThrive, LLC (“AdThrive”) for the purposes of placing advertising on the site.  AdThrive uses standard and widely-available tools for the placement and serving of ads, including those provided by Google, Inc. and its affiliates. We publish interest-based advertisements on the site; that is, ads that are tailored to reflect your interests. To help understand your interests, AdThrive, Google, and our other advertising partners will track your behaviour on our website and on other websites across the Internet using cookies.

A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. Cookies may be either persistent or session. A persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date. A session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the session, when the web browser is closed. Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but the information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.

By using this site, you consent to the use of such cookies and the sharing of data captured by such cookies with AdThrive, Google, and our other third-party partners. You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser by visiting: [https://adssettings.google.com](https://adssettings.google.com/). You can also opt out of the network cookie using those settings or using the Network Advertising Initiative’s multi-cookie opt-out mechanism at [http://optout.networkadvertising.org](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/). However, these opt-out mechanisms themselves use cookies, and if you clear the cookies from your browser, your opt-out will not be maintained.

### For European Economic Area Residents

If you reside in a country in the European Economic Area (EEA), then under the GDPR and applicable data protection laws you have the rights, among other things, to access your personal data, have us erase it, and/or restrict its further processing.  If you wish to access or delete your personal data (if any) maintained by us or AdThrive related to advertising on the site, you can contact us at [admin@healthykitchen101.com](mailto:admin@healthykitchen101.com) and contact AdThrive at [info@adthrive.com](mailto:info@adthrive.com). If you wish to see a list of the advertising partners we work with or change which of those partners are allowed to track your behavior using cookies, click the ad preferences link at the bottom of the site.
